(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Wait, this is good.
I did it!
I infiltrated this place!
Success!
大作戦！
The big mission!
あ、みんなに見られた！
Ah, everyone saw me!
I can't believe you guys were watching me
this whole time! No!
To be honest, I did feel... I did feel eyes on me,
but I knew you guys were watching, it's okay.
Anyways, it's not the time to be talking
about that because
today is a special day for me! Whee! Yeah!
Do you know what today is?
Say it, say it! Say it, say it!
Yeah, today is my birthday!
Happy birthday Zeta, happy birthday Zeta,
Selamat ulang tahun Zeta.
Happy birthday, Zeta.
こんな感じだっけ？
Is that how it goes?
I don't know. Well...
Oh, what? You're saying something? Huh?
Mmm, nope.
Skill issue!
You're saying I'm a noob as a secret agent?
Bulls... Okay, I can't say the rest. Bulls.
Your lies, you're lying! That can't be true.
I've been working hard. I've got the stamina,
and obviously the intelligence,
IQ 二百！
IQ 200!
And strength, you know?
Got the power as well. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So anyways, don't you worry because
I've got the perfect thing for today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Have you ever heard of a...
of a secret agent school?
Yeah, so... back in my days, back in my days,
I've been through hell and back,
so I invited some tests for students here
so we can prove that I'm the best secret agent, okay?
So, we're going to do some tests together to see
how tough it is to become a professional
secret agent like me, like me, like me!
I'm a good example.
Anyways, it reminds me of my old gakko-ism,
Anyways, it reminds me of my old school days,
you know? But to be honest, to be honest...
To be honest, I don't know what we'll be doing yet, but...
Wait, oh crap! Okay,
it's almost time for the first test!
最初のテストか... そろそろ...
Is it the first test? Soon...
あ！早く行かないと！
Ah! I have to go fast!
Bye!
来るなー！
Don't come!
なんかさ...
Hey...
あれ？なんか...
Wait, something...
みこちのカマキリの威嚇ポーズにビビってる。
It's scared of Miko-chi's praying mantis intimidation pose.
ビビってる、ビビってる。プルプル。
It's shaking with fear.
これみこちゃんわかりました。
I've got it.
コイツ雑魚ゾンビです。
This guy is a weakling zombie.
ざぁ～こ
Nooooob.
コイツどMかも知れん。
He might be a major masochist.
どMゾンビかも。
Maybe a masochist zombie.
ポンコツ～
Useless~
もしかして... じゃみこちゃんも言っていい？
Perhaps... Can I say it too?
みこちゃんも言って。
You go ahead and say it too.
ざぁ～こ
Nooooob.
ちょっとヨワヨワゾンビさんなんじゃない？
Isn't he a bit of a weakling zombie?
なんじゃないですか？全然怖くないんですけど。
Isn't he? I'm not scared at all though.
ヨワヨワ～
So weak~
あー、みんな！
Ah, everyone!
遅れてごめーん！
Sorry I'm late!
なにこのゾンビ？
What is this zombie?
あれはヨワヨワゾンビ。
That's a weakling zombie.
エージェントスクールの最初のテストにお招きしたけど、
I invited you for the first test of the Agent School,
ゾンビも新入生なのかな？
but I wonder if the zombie is also a new student?
新入生？！
A new student?!
そうだ、でも言葉通じないけどさ、ゾンビに。
Right, but we can't communicate with the zombie.
ゼータは言葉いろんな言葉話せるよね。
Zeta, you can speak many different languages, right?
ゾンビ語もしゃべれるんじゃないの？
Can't you speak Zombie-ish too?
えー！ちょっと待って、待って。
Wait, wait a minute.
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
ちょっと弱そうかも。
He seems a bit weak.
会話してる！
They're having a conversation!
よし、できた。
Alright, I did it.
できた？！
You did it?!
おい！ゾンビ！
Hey! Zombie!
何してるの！
What are you doing?!
怖がらせろって言ったでしょ？！
I told you to be scary, didn't I?!
ほんとに何やってたのよ！
What have you been doing?!
ごめんあそばせ。
Apologies.
どうやら弱っちいゾンビを送っちゃったみたいね。
I probably sent over the weak zombies.
申し訳ないわね。
Sorry about that.
さて、今日はみなさんにサプライズテストをご用意しました。
Anyways, I called you guys here for a surprise test.
シークレットエージェントにふさわしいか、確かめてみましょう。
To see if you guys are fit to be a secret agent.
なんか分かんないけど受ける。
I don't really get it, but I'll take it.
なんか分かんないけど受けてみるか。
Should we try taking it?
受けてみよう。
Let's try.
さてさて、みなさん落ち着いてくださいね。
Okay, okay, calm down everyone.
では、この箱の中身を当ててもらうテストになります！
In this test, you will need to guess what is inside the box!
箱の中身！
Guess what's inside!
ラウンド1では、30秒だけ中身に触れられます。
For round 1, you can feel the object for 30 seconds only.
楽しんでくださいね。
Have fun.
みなさんのリアクション、すっごく楽しみですね。
Can't wait to see your reactions.
いいリアクション期待してるよだって。
She says she's expecting good reactions.
完全に馬鹿にしてるから。
She's totally making fun of us.
当たり前じゃん。
Of course she is.
じゃあAZKi先輩からかな？
Will we start with AZKi-senpai?
任せてくださいよ。
Please leave it to me.
これはさ、みんなで協力してだよね。
We should all cooperate on this, right?
伝えることに集中したいと思います。
I'll focus on communicating what I feel.
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
Three, two, one, start!
うわ！え？これ？
Whoa! Wait, this?
えっと、コードのような...
Um, it's like a cord...
コード？
A cord?
ちょっと待って、なにこれ！
Wait a minute, what is this!
Frog toy
なんかじたばたしてます、じたばた。
It's flailing around, flailing.
じたばた？動いてる！
Flailing? It's moving!
え、なんか動いている...けど...！
Eh, it's moving... but...!
Time's up!
フォルムがわからない。
I can't tell the shape.
なんか足がバタバタしてるみたい。
It felt like legs were kicking.
バタバタ？えー！
Kicking? Whoa!
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
じゃ、ミオしゃ、start!
Then, Mio-sha, start!
あ！あ！何か気づいた。
Ah! I noticed something.
でも分かったかもこれうち。
But I think I might have figured it out.
あー、はいはいはい...
Ah, yes yes yes...
あー、元気ですね。
Ah, it's very energetic.
完全に生きてますよ。
It's definitely alive.
Time's up!
あー元気だったな、すごい元気だった。
Ah, it was energetic, really energetic.
絶対生きてるんだ。
It's definitely alive.
さくらみこの挑戦
Sakura Miko's Challenge
ゴッドハンドみこ
God Hand Miko...
ゴッドハンドみこです！
...God Hand Miko is here!
頑張って！
Do your best!
3, 2, 1...
Go!
え、虫絶対やだ
Wait, I definitely don't want bugs.
ギャーーー！
AAAHHH!
何かに触れた模様
Looks like she touched something.
ギャーーー！
AAAHHH!
やめて、マジですか？
Stop it, are you serious?
ガチなやつ、ガチなやつ
This is for real, this is for real.
ねぇ、やめて！
Hey, stop it!
真剣な表情
A serious expression.
わかった？
Did you figure it out?
全然わかんない
I have no idea.
Time's up!
全然わかんない
I have no idea.
終わりだよ
It's over.
え、ゴッドハンド？
Eh, God Hand?
ゴッドハンド？
God Hand?
ブルルッてなって
It went "brrrr"...
めっちゃきもい！
It was so gross!
じゃあ次はゼータ！
Alright, next is Zeta!
じゃあ次はゼータ、行け！
Alright, next is Zeta, go!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Bestia Zeta's Challenge
行きますよ
Here I go.
行きます！
Going!
3, 2, 1...
Start!
うわ、何これ？
Whoa, what's this?
え、これ生きてるやん
Eh, this is alive.
多分生きてない気がするけど
I have a feeling it's probably not alive, but...
え、何これ？
Eh, what is this?
今、結構触っています
She's touching it quite a bit now.
何これ？
What is this?
え、飛んでる？
Eh, is it flying?
これ飛んでる？
Is this flying?
なんか飛びそうではあるよね
It does look like it's about to fly.
飛びそうだよね
It looks like it might fly.
飛びそう
Looks like it'll fly...
生きてる…！
It's alive...!
Time's up!
生きているのかなんなのか
Is it alive or what?
いやー、これちょっと
Man, this is a bit...
でもこれみんなでね
But everyone, together...
力を合わせて
...combine our strength.
誰か一人でも当てればってことで
As long as at least one of us gets it.
プロペラがついたもの？
Something with a propeller?
何か付いてたのかなって
I wondered if something was attached.
マジでみこが手を入れた時に
Seriously, when Miko put her hand in...
ブルルッてなったから
...it went "brrrr"!
アヒルの玩具
A duck toy
アヒルとかの足がこう
Like the feet of a duck...
バタバタバタってなってる
...going flap flap flap.
バタバタバタみたいな
Like "batabata"...
なんかそういうおもちゃ
Some kind of toy like that.
ミオ先輩は？
How about Mio-senpai?
これはズバリ
This is, without a doubt...
カエルの玩具
A frog toy
カエルの玩具です
...a frog toy.
ぴょこぴょこ
Hop hop hop.
ブルブルしてたってこと？
So it was vibrating?
ゼータちゃん、みんなの回答まとめ
Zeta-chan, summarize everyone's answers.
え、答えまとめてください
Eh, please summarize the answer.
ミオ先輩の答えで
With Mio-senpai's answer.
自信満々だったもんね
She was so confident, wasn't she?
自信満々だった、間違ってたらド戦犯だわ
So confident. If it's wrong, I'm a total culprit.
解答：カエルの玩具
Answer: Frog toy
カエルの玩具かな
I guess it's a frog toy.
みんなのあれだからね
It's based on everyone's input.
じゃあ、カエルの玩具ね
Okay, so a frog toy.
Good guess, that's correct!
あ、よくできました！
Oh, well done!
正解！
Correct!
当ってる！すごい！
You got it! Amazing!
カエルの玩具だ！
It's a frog toy!
すごい、ミオちゃん
Amazing, Mio-chan.
何がポイントなんですか？
What was the giveaway?
触った感じがピタピタしてて
It felt all sticky when I touched it.
そのピタピタ感もヒントで
That sticky feeling was a hint.
なんか、ぴょんぴょんしてたから
And it was kind of jumping around.
これカエルの玩具っぽいなって思ったんだよね
So I thought, "This seems like a frog toy."
すごい！
Amazing!
素晴らしい
Wonderful.
じゃあ次の問題
Alright, next question.
お願いします
Please.
じゃあうちが行ってみますか？
Should I go next?
ゴッドハンドミオ
God Hand Mio.
行きますか、ゴッドハンドミオに
Shall we go with God Hand Mio?
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
頑張れ、ミオちゃん！
Go for it, Mio-chan!
怖い、怖い！
Scared, scared!
ほら！
Look!
相当怖がっている
She looks really scared.
嘘でしょ、何これ？
No way, what's this?
これ、何なんだろうこれ、気持ち悪い
This... what is this, it's gross.
気持ち悪い
It's gross.
何これ？何これ？
What's this? What's this?
怖い、怖い、怖い
Scared, scared, scared.
わかった、わかったんじゃないの、その反応
I get it, doesn't that reaction mean she knows?
そういうこと？
Is that so?
Time's up!
いや、いや！
No, no!
大げさにやってるでしょ
You're exaggerating, right?
全然！
Not at all!
なんかやだ
I don't like it.
ちょっと行ってみて、行ってみて
Give it a try, give it a try.
AZKi先輩、頑張って
AZKi-senpai, do your best.
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
やっぱそうだよね
I thought so.
何、何？
What, what?
いやその反応になるって
Man, that's exactly the reaction.
モシャモシャしてます
It feels shaggy/fuzzy.
ヒントは？
Any hints?
モシャモシャ
Shaggy/Fuzzy.
なんかベタベタしてた
It was kind of sticky.
何それ？キモい
What's that? Gross.
でもこれ多分
But this, probably...
これは何かのパーツって言われたらムズいんだけど
If you asked me what part this is, it'd be hard.
Time's up!
なんかちょっと心にダメージ受けるよね、これ
It kind of damages your heart a bit, this thing.
次行くか！
Next one!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Bestia Zeta's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
うわぁ！
Waaa!
初手驚くよね
You're surprised at first, right?
そうそう
Yeah, yeah.
最初は驚くよね、これ
You're surprised at first by this.
えー？
Eh?
でも、柔らかい、柔らかい
But it's soft, soft.
柔らかい
Soft.
優しい
Gentle.
優しい？
Gentle?
優しい、柔らかい
Gentle, soft.
これに関してはちょっとね、ゼタの感覚が狂ってるかも...
Regarding this, maybe Zeta's sense is a bit off...
えー？
Eh?
なに、なに、なに？ 余計に怖いんだけど
What, what, what? That makes it even scarier.
え、いいのかここで？
Eh, is it okay here?
いいのか？ いいのかここで？ うん。
Is it okay? Is it okay here? Hmm.
じゃあ、みこ先輩頑張ってね
Then, Miko-senpai, good luck.
待って、待って
Wait, wait.
出た、出た！ ゴットハンド！
It's out, it's out! God Hand!
いや、これゴットリアクション...
No, this is a God Reaction...
ゴットリアクション来るか？ じゃあ
Will a God Reaction come? Then...
スタート！
Start!
来た、ゴットリアクション！ 出た！
It's here, God Reaction! It came out!
待って待って、ためらっています
Wait wait, she's hesitating.
手を入れることをためらっているが
She's hesitating to put her hand in, but...
ためらうよね、これ！ 痛いもん！
You'd hesitate, right?! It hurts!
マジなんか、生き物じゃないか
Seriously, isn't it like a living thing?
そう、生き物... 待って何これ
Yeah, living thing... Wait, what is this?
ゾクッとするような...
Makes you shiver...
食べ物？ いやそんなことはない
Food? No, that can't be it.
まさか...
No way...
うわ、なんか出てる！ 待って待って待って
Uwa, something's coming out! Wait wait wait.
ちょっとヤバイことが起きてるじゃないか
Isn't something bad happening?
ヤバイこと？
Something bad?
あの箱の中で
Inside that box.
事件が起きている
An incident is happening.
マスクをしてたと思うんだよね
I think it was wearing a mask.
だから、ピエロのマスクなんじゃないかと思いました
So I thought, maybe it's a clown mask.
えっと、白い、白塗りの女性の、顔...
Um, a white, white-painted woman's face...
こえーよ！ マスク？ マスクか？
Scary! Mask? Is it a mask?
白塗りの女性のマスク
A white-painted woman's mask.
その答えこえーよ！
That answer is scary!
おそらく、うん
Probably, yeah.
YAGOOのカツラ
YAGOO's wig.
えー？！
Eh?!
絶対カツラだったと思うんだよ、あれ
I'm sure that was a wig.
ロングヘアーYAGOO？
Long hair YAGOO?
そう、ロングヘアーYAGOO
Yeah, long hair YAGOO.
そうだよ、可能性高いかも...
That's right, the possibility might be high...
名探偵みこ先輩に信じようかな
I guess I'll believe Detective Miko-senpai.
答えは...
The answer is...
ロングヘアーYAGOO！
Long hair YAGOO!
あっちゃー、残念だね
Uh-oh, too bad.
不正解です！
Wrong answer!
なんか怖いんだけど
Something's scary though.
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
当たってるよ！
I got it right!
ミオちゃん当たってるよ、当たってるよ...
Mio-chan got it right, she got it right...
当たってる！ 当たってるの怖い、怖い
She got it! It's scary that she got it right...
次の問題お願いします
Next question, please.
お願いします！
Please!
じゃあ、こちらみこちゃんが行ってみますか
Then, shall Miko-chan try this one?
名探偵、決めてね、ここで
Detective, decide it here.
名探偵、頼むよ
Detective, I'm counting on you.
ゴーゴーゴー！ スタート！
Go go go! Start!
待って、待って、濡れてる！
Wait, wait, it's wet!
ちょっと今日一の絶叫出たけど大丈夫？
The biggest scream of the day just came out, are you okay?
え？ え？
Eh? Eh?
実況してよ！ 実況、実況！
Commentate! Commentary, commentary!
なんかチクチクしてて... 痛い
Something's prickly... it hurts.
痛いの？
It hurts?
ぬるぬるのが濡れてて...
Slimey and wet...
濡れてる？ 濡れてる！
Wet? It's wet!
全部に、トゲトゲがあります
There are thorns everywhere.
全部にトゲトゲがある？
There are thorns everywhere?
いっぱい、生き物...
Lots of, living thing...
トゲトゲした生き物がいっぱいいるって何？
What do you mean by lots of prickly living things?
何何何？ 怖かった、いっぱいいる
What what what? It was scary, there are many.
どうする？ AZKi先輩の方がいいかな？
What should we do? Maybe AZKi-senpai is better?
冷静な判断できるのかな？
Can she make a calm judgment?
AZKi先輩、ゴー！
AZKi-senpai, go!
はい！ スタート！
Yes! Start!
え、何？ お？ お？
Eh, what? Oh? Oh?
なんか濡れてる
Something's wet.
濡れてる、やっぱ濡れてるんだ
Wet, so it really is wet.
え、なんか湿って、湿っています
Eh, it's kind of damp, damp.
湿っている... 湿度高めなんだ、これ
Damp... The humidity is high in this one.
え、何これ
Eh, what is this?
え、何この... トゲトゲした球体のような...
Eh, what is this... like a prickly sphere...
球体？ 球体とその下にもトゲトゲしたものが？
A sphere? A sphere and there's also something prickly underneath?
トゲトゲがいっぱいある、痛くはないけど
There are many thorns, though it doesn't hurt.
痛くはない？
It doesn't hurt?
え、これ何だ？ 何なんだろう、わからん、全然わからん
Eh, what is this? I wonder what it is, I don't know at all.
めちゃムズいんだ、じゃあ
Then it's super hard.
何だこれー！ えー！ なんか湿ってるー！
What is this! Eh! It's kind of damp!
ミオちゃんですかね、次
Is it Mio-chan next?
最後、ゼタに決めてもらおう
Lastly, let's have Zeta decide.
やだ、その感想聞いた状態で触るのちょっとやだかも
I don't really want to touch it after hearing those impressions.
ゴー！
Go!
やだー、濡れてるって前情報でやだ
I hate this, I hate the prior info that it's wet.
濡れてるよ、頑張って
It's wet, good luck.
ああ、やっぱ... 濡れてるなー
Ah, as I thought... it's wet.
濡れてる？ 濡れてる？ おお、濡れてる
Wet? Wet? Oh, it's wet.
けど... 濡れてるけど、なんか硬くて
But... it's wet but, it's kind of hard.
硬くて... 確かにたくさんいる
Hard... certainly there are many.
たくさんいるぞ！ 一体何なんだよー
There are many! What on earth is it?
これは何だ？
What is this?
え、これでもさ、あんまり見かけないやつな気がする
Eh, but this, I feel like it's something you don't see very often.
見かけない、見かけない...
Don't see it, don't see it...
ああ、むず！
Ah, it's hard!
これむずいんじゃない？
Isn't this going to be hard?
え、むずい！
Eh, it's hard!
むずいんだ！むずいんだ！
It's hard! It's hard!
ゼタ！行け！
Zeta! Go!
頑張れゼタ！
Good luck, Zeta!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
我々にしたらちょっと難しいかも
It might be a bit difficult for us.
タイムアップ！イエーイ！
Time's up! Yay!
THINKING TIME
おそらくこれは
Probably, this is...
ウニの仲間
A relative of the sea urchin.
ウニ！？
Sea urchin!?
苔
Moss.
みこの答えは ライチ！
Miko's answer is... Lychee!
ゼタはね、たぶん…
Zeta thinks, maybe...
インドネシアの果物と近いかも
It's similar to an Indonesian fruit.
名前はランブータン
Its name is Rambutan.
自信持って！ゼタが一番わかってた！
Have confidence! Zeta knew it best!
解答：ランブータン
Answer: Rambutan
ピンポーン！正解でーす！
Ding ding ding! Correct answer!
Rambutan
正解の答えも不正解の答えもありましたね
There seems to have been correct and incorrect answers.
でも… ゼータ！
But... Zeta!
どうやらあなたの推理力はまだまだみたいだね？
It seems like your investigative skills are not quite up to par yet.
もっと頑張らないと
You need to work harder.
つまり、そう……
Or, in other words...
スキルの問題ね！
Skill issue! Hahaha!
見て、スキルが問題のゼータだって！
Oh, look at her with the skill issues!
あっ、怒っちゃった！
She's getting mad! Hahaha!
あらあら！
Oh dear!
まったく、こんなのも解けないなんて！
Wow, you can't even solve that!
みんな、よくやったわ！
Everyone else, you did great!
次のテストも頑張ってくださいね！
Good luck on the next test!
またね！
See y'all!
もっと床に這いつくばりなさい
Crawl on the floor some more.
Wait, there's like a ring. Wait, is this like a boxing ring?
Wait, what am I gonna have to do here?
No way, are we gonna have to fight? I'm not good at fighting though.
Happy Birthday, Zeta!
Long time no see!
This is Amelia Watson.
hololive EN's number one time-traveling detective!
How've you been?
I've been good! How are you?
Ah, glad to see you're doing well!
Yeah, I prepared the second test,
but we also have other transfer students.
Let's call them in now!
Don't let the first contestant's size fool you!
その名前とあの名セリフを聞けば、誰もが思わず震え上がるんです！
People tremble when they hear her name and her infamous line!
「小さくてもパワフル、その強さはまさに本物の宝石！レッツ・ロック！」
"Small but mighty, always rock hard. I'm rocking in!"
ご紹介しましょう……古石ビジュー！
Please welcome... Koseki Bijou!
ハッピーバースデー、ゼータ！
Happy Birthday Zeta!
今日は君のためにカッチカチだよ。
Today I'm rock hard just for you.
私たちが望んだヒーローではないかもしれませんが、なぜか信じたくなってしまう存在です！
She's the hero we didn't ask for, but somehow still believe in!
ほかのいいヒーローたちが忙しい中、最後の希望として現れたのが彼女！
She's everyone's last hope, because all the good ones were busy!
彼女のセリフは……『滅びを迎え、絶望せよ！はあっ！』
Her line is: "Meet your end, and... despair! Haiyah!"
ハッピーバースデー、ゼータ！
Happy Birthday Zeta!
君を奈落の底に……叩き落としてあげる。
I'm taking you down... down... under.
ダンベルは隠してプライドは防御してください！
Ladies and gentlemen, hide your dumbbells and protect your ego!
次に登場するのは魂を狩るだけでなく、ジムまでぶっ壊しちゃう死神なんです！
Because this grim reaper doesn't just reap souls, she rips the gym apart!
彼女の好きなセリフは……『時間だけが、あたしに勝てるベンチプレスよ！』
Her favorite line is, "Only time can out-bench me."
ご紹介しましょう……森カリオペ！
Please welcome... Mori Calliope!
ハッピーバースデー、ゼータ！
Happy Birthday Zeta!
よいしょ！みんな集まりましたね？
Good! Everyone has gathered, right?
これにはきっとびっくりした人も多いんじゃないでしょうか？
This is probably a big surprise, huh?
そして、みんな気になってますよね！いったいどんなテストなのか！
And I'm sure you're all wondering what kind of test this is gonna be!
さて、みんな予想はありますか？
Anyone have any guesses?
床叩きじゃないですよ？
Don't say ground pounding.
あっ、正解です！
Oh, correct!
今回は、この長い棒にBazoくんの重りをつけて挑戦です！
We're holding a physical test using this long stick with these Bazo weights
シークレットエージェントとして通用する身体能力があるかをテストします！
to determine if you are fit enough to pass off as a secret agent!
体力テストのレベル1、いきましょう！
For level 1 of the physical test!
まずは、このBazoくんをマットから腰の高さまで、できるだけ多く持ち上げてください！
First, lift Bazo from the ring mat up to your hips as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
レベル2では、マットがデコボコになります！
For level 2, the mat will be bumpy!
前と同じように、できるだけ多く持ち上げてください！
You'll do the same thing as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
そして最後のレベルでは、デコボコマットの上に立って頭の上にカップを乗せます！
And for the last level, you'll stand on the bumpy mat and balance a cup on your head!
カップを落とさないように、Bazoくんを持ち上げてください！
Make sure you don't drop it, and lift Bazo up!
それでは、みんな準備はいいですか？
Well then, are you guys ready?
さあ、レッツゴー！
Let's go!
よし、体力テストの準備はいいですか？
Okay, who's ready for the physical test?
まずはビジューからいきましょうか？
Okay, maybe we should have Bijou start first?
任せて！岩のように硬い筋肉を見せてあげる！
I got it! She's rocking her rock hard muscles!
位置について、用意、スタート！
Ready, set, go!
（カウント：1〜21回）
(Counting: 1 to 21)
終了！
Time's up!
ビジュー！レベル1、21回！
Bijou! Level 1: 21!
次はアイリス！
Now IRyS!
任せて！見返してやるんだから！
I got this! I'm gonna prove them wrong!
スタート！
Start!
（カウント：1〜21回）
(Counting: 1 to 21)
終了！
Time's up!
アイリス！レベル1、21回！
IRyS! Level 1: 21!
Like I said, it's more of a speed thing, isn't it?
Show us! Ready? Start!
1!
2!
3!
4!
5!
6!
7!
8!
9!
10!
11!
12!
13!
Oh my god! 14!
15!
16!
17!
She's locking in! 18!
19!
20!
21!
22!
23!
Oh my god! 24!
25!
26!
27!
28!
29!
Time's up!
Anyway, that was me, 29!
29! Nice!
Okay, you have to show us what you're made of.
I got this.
Okay, okay, okay. You're gonna count down for me?
Of course. You ready? Yeah! Start!
1!
2!
3!
4!
5!
6!
7!
8!
9!
10!
11!
12!
13!
14!
15!
16!
17!
18!
19!
Dang! 20!
21!
22!
23!
24!
25!
26!
27!
28!
29!
30!
Time's up!
Whoa! That was some exercise!
I can't stand up!
You did great!
But but but, I'm the secret agent after all!
I feel my soul left out of my body.
That's enough workout for this year.
Yeah.
Okay, now who's ready for Level 2?
I don't know about this one.
Wait a minute, that's not fair!
Those are pebbles!
That's not fair! She has the advantage!
Pebbles! I'm loving it! They're loving it!
Oh, it hurts so... Oh my god, I...
Okay, start!
1!
2!
3!
4!
5!
6!
7!
8!
9!
10!
11!
12!
13!
14!
15!
16!
17!
18!
19!
20!
21!
22!
23!
24!
25!
26!
27!
28!
29!
30!
31!
32!
33!
34!
Time's up!
Great! How much was that?
Was that her full power?
Listen to the rocks, they gave me strength!
One is running away! Help her!
Show them who you are! Prove to the world!
You have some time to get comfortable.
Take your time. How does it feel? How does it feel?
Tell me when you're ready. Ready? Start!
1!
2!
3!
Ow! 4!
5!
6!
7!
8!
9! I did it! 10!
11!
12!
13! 14!
15!
16!
17!
18!
19!
20!
Time's up!
You did it! You don't have to keep standing there.
She's lost for words. I think she's...
20. I'm not gonna go that hard.
The pebbles are gonna help me out, so...
Alright, well, I'll try to just do my best.
You got this! Oh, ouch!
Alright, I'm good. Okay, start!
1!
2!
3!
4!
5!
6!
7!
Ouch! 8!
9!
10!
11!
12!
13!
14!
15!
Go fast! 16!
17!
18!
19!
20!
21!
22!
23!
24!
25!
26!
27!
28!
29!
30!
31! 32!
Time's up!
Whoo! I did it!
You got more than your first time!
32! Nice!
Yeah, your form was perfect!
I think it was 33! I counted 33!
So the final count was...
eight...?
The final count is thirty-two!
Yay! I'll take it.
Step on those pebbles like they're ones!
Wait, who gives you permission?
Yeah, Bibo gives me permission!
She's gonna step on 'em.
She's going Super Saiyan!
やべぇ...
This is bad...
Something's coming out of me!
Okay, Zeta, are you ready?
Three, two, one, Go!
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight, nine...
Ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen...
Fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen...
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty, twenty-one...
Twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five...
Twenty-six, twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine, thirty...
Thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three, thirty-four...
Thirty-five, thirty-six, thirty-seven!
Time's up!
Zeta... level 38! Amazing!
I'm glad you guys are having fun!
Level 3 of the physical test is gonna be pretty tough, though.
You guys ready?
For level 3, I've got a little something...
behind me, which is a...
A cup!
Would you like a cup of tea?
Maybe later!
While we are stepping on the bumpy mat...
we're also gonna be balancing this on top of our head like this.
Yes! You'll have to use the mat.
It's a combination of everything.
Yeah! And while lifting as well, of course.
It doesn't affect us at all!
Crown the princess.
Oh! There you go.
It's so over... it's so over.
Remember to use your butt and your legs.
The core is important!
Okay, core! Ready?
Ready! Three, two, one, Start!
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen...
Sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen...
Twenty, twenty-one, twenty-two...
Twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five...
Twenty-six, twenty-seven!
Time's up!
The cup was stuck on her head!
That was funny! And it was hot on her head!
Twenty-eight! You got twenty-eight!
IRyS, it's time!
IRyS, the princess! Beautiful posture.
Exactly! Shown in her posture.
She's very good at keeping it on her head.
Wait a second, don't put it on me yet!
Okay, you may place it on my head.
Here goes... thank you. Oh, it's beautiful.
Not to my coronation!
Three, two, one, Start!
One, two, three...
Four, five, six...
Seven, eight, nine...
Ten! Keep going!
Oh my god, I'm already about to cry.
Nine, ten, eleven...
Twelve... I don't know how you guys did this!
Time's up!
Proud of you! This stupid cup!
Don't blame the cup!
Maybe my good form will come in handy here.
Yeah, exactly! Place the tiara on my head.
Now you have to step on it first.
It's the pain before the gain.
Pain is beauty!
I shall place it on top of the crown.
Awesome! Okay, beautiful.
Are you ready, Calli?
Three, two, one, Start!
One, two, three, four...
Five!
6, 7
8, 9
10!
11, 12
13, 14, 15
16, 17, 18
19, 20!
21, 22, 23
24, 25!
Time's up!
Yes! That's my goal!
That's what I'm talking about!
Yeah, that's 24! And I didn't lose the cup once.
You sure did. Maybe this cup was taped on.
Maybe there was tape! I think she's cheating.
Is it not? Superglue? Was it superglue?
Put it on IRyS's head. Put it on...
Let's really test it. Let's really get in there.
You're gonna use me as the test? Yeah.
It's Zeta's turn. Zeta, birthday girl!
Directly right in the center of your head...
...so that it's less likely to fall off.
This is like the best birthday ever.
Oh, yay! I'm glad.
Now then, are you ready?
Three, two, one, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
Time's up!
Yay! You did it! 26!
26 is your final number. Zeta, Level 3: 26.
No way! Yay! Wow!
Does this mean the scores are what I think it is?
I think so!
Is anyone keeping score?
The staff-san has been keeping score for us.
Yay! You are a winner!
I am a winner! Yeah!
It's all about how you feel though.
What matters is what's inside.
Seems like you guys completed the test! Woohoo!
Some of you were able to lift pretty well.
Maybe not for some, though.
It was so much fun just watching!
But come on, Zeta. You're the birthday girl!
You should be showing us your crazy skills!
Prove it to us next test, okay?
Well then, thank you for having me!
This is Amelia Watson signing off.
Until next time! Bye!
She just has really high standards, okay?
Even if you won... not enough for her.
She is a detective after all.
Everyone needs to be better! Let's go!
La+ Darknesss!
あいつを狙おう！
Okay, let's aim at that one!
Ah! Oh! Ow! Stop it!
She fell down! No! Help!
Stop it! This is scary!
It's too much! Stop!
Level 1 clear!
Level 2! No way!
Tokoyami Towa! So fun, so fun!
Zeta! What? What? Why are you holding guns?
Yay! Aim at her! No! Stop!
What is this? I'm scared!
Stop! Hold on! Hold on!
What are you doing? No!
どういうこと？誰か説明して〜
What do you mean? Someone explain!
Bokobokobo~ Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Zeta, happy birthday! Thank you!
I already told them what to do before you came here.
We're gonna be testing your aim with this water gun!
In shooting level 1, we will see how many targets you hit!
In level 2, we see how many moving targets you hit!
And level 3 will test you against a moving zombie!
Who do you think is the best shooter here?
Me! Me! Me!
We all play FPS, so... That's right!
I don't play it though! Haha!
がんばろ、がんばろ
Let's do our best, let's do our best.
次はどういう感じなんですか？
What's the next part going to be like?
負けませんよ
I won't lose!
負けないよ
I won't lose either!
Level 1
こちらに
Over here...
動かない的があるので、こちらをみんなで一人ずつ打っていこうかなと思います
...there are stationary targets, so let's all take turns shooting them one by one.
がんばるー
I'll do my best!
はい！
Yes!
順番どうしましょう？
What should we do about the order?
やりたいやりたいやりたい！
I want to go! I want to go! I want to go!
まつりちゃんはいい位置に待ってもらって...
Matsuri-chan, please wait in a good position...
トワさんにはここら辺で見てもらってましょう
Let's have Towa-san watch from around here.
はーい
Okay!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
Start!
おお、うまっ！
Oh, she's good!
うめぇ！
She's good!
うめっ！
Good!
外さなし！
No misses!
まつさんがパーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't Matsu-san 'Perfect Old Man'?
パーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't she 'Perfect Old Man'?
うますぎる！やばい！
She's too good! Crazy!
残り15秒！
15 seconds left!
えー、これみんなには分かんないけど、すげー難しいんだからね、これ
You guys might not realize it, but this is really hard!
すごいすごい、偏差とかもなしに
Amazing, amazing, without even any lead time.
え、パーフェクト？パーフェクト？
Wait, perfect? Perfect?
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まつりちゃんは一発も外さず、すべて取れました！
Matsuri-chan got them all without missing a single shot!
Clear
すごーい！うますぎるよね
Amazing! She's way too good.
ちょっと行きづらいわー
It's hard to go after that...
次私行こ！
I'll go next!
やったー、トワ様でしょ、次
Yay, it's Towa-sama next, right?
次トワ様だ！
Next is Towa-sama!
トワ、がんばれー
Towa, good luck!
支えるよ、支える感じで
I'll support you, like a brace.
じゃあ、カウント3、2...
Okay, counting down. 3, 2...
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
ここ！
Here!
おお！早い早い！
Oh! Fast, fast!
早い！
Fast!
トワ様早い！
Towa-sama is fast!
えー！
Wait!
ちょっと待って、どういうこと？うまい、めっちゃ早い！
Wait a sec, what's going on? She's good, so fast!
うまい！
Good!
早すぎる！
Too fast!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Clear
だんだん超えてくんだ、これ
It keeps getting better and better.
次どうする？
What's next?
いや、先にやっといた方がいい
No, it's better to get it over with first.
下半身作戦、下半身作戦！
Lower body strategy, lower body strategy!
下半身を安定させ、ぶれないようにする
Stabilize the lower body to keep from shaking.
下半身作戦だと言ったな？
Lower body strategy, you said?
ポーズダセェ！
That pose is lame!
ダサすぎる！
Too lame!
これでいくから！
I'm going with this!
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, Go!
うおら！
Uora!
がんばれ、がんばれ...
Good luck, good luck...
安定させて...
Keep it stable...
やー！適当に打つ！
Ya! I'll just shoot randomly!
あ、でも惜しい惜しい！
Ah, but that was close, close!
がんばれ、がんばれ...
Good luck, good luck...
もっと上、もっと上！
Higher, higher!
がんばって、がんばって！いいよ、それ空だぞ！
Do your best! Okay, that's just the sky!
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
ラプラスの結果は、まあ、2ポイントとなりましたー
Laplus's result is, well, 2 points!
最後、いきますか！
Last one, shall we go?
いくぞー！がんばれー！
Let's go! Good luck!
ということで、最後ゼタ、打ちましょう
So, finally Zeta, let's have you shoot.
1秒で、1秒で...
In 1 second, in 1 second...
準備OK！
Ready!
いくよ、じゃあ、3、2、1、ゴー！
Here we go. 3, 2, 1, Go!
うわー！
Uwaa!
おおー、いいよ、いいよ！
Oh, nice, nice!
すごい！
Amazing!
うまいよー！
You're good!
残り15秒！
15 seconds left!
全然余裕余裕！
Totally easy, easy!
あと一個！あと一個！どこだ？どこだ？
One more! One more! Where is it? Where is it?
右、右、下！そっちそっち！
Right, right, down! That way, that way!
下見て、下見て！
Look down, look down!
どこだ？
Where is it?
どこだ？え、なくなった？
Where is it? Eh, did it disappear?
いや、な、何これ？守護霊が...
No, wha- what is this? A guardian spirit...
神様が手伝ってもらったのかな、まさか
Maybe God helped her out?
まつり先輩ナイスショット！
Matsuri-senpai, nice shot!
なんかギリギリ滑り込みで、1敗取れた！イェーイ！
Somehow I squeezed it in at the last second! Yay!
Clear
Level 2
あちらをご覧ください！
Please look over there!
動いてる！何これ？動いてる！
They're moving! What's this? They're moving!
はい、がんばっていきましょう！
Okay, let's do our best!
じゃあ、誰からいく？
Okay, who's going first?
俺だ俺だ俺だ！私もいきたい！
Me! Me! Me! I want to go too!
もう行っちゃったから、じゃあラプラスからね
She's already moved, so let's start with Laplus.
やったもん勝ちでやばい
First come first served is crazy.
ではいきましょう、ラプラス！いきますよ！
Alright, let's go, Laplus! Here we go!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
このゲームには必勝法がある！
There's a winning strategy to this game!
めっちゃ回っとるやん！
She's spinning a lot!
後ろから撃ってるのヤバいって！
Shooting from behind is crazy!
当たってないよ！
You're not hitting!
撃て！撃て！撃て！
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
ぐるんぐるんだからカメラ
The camera is spinning around.
あと5秒しかないよ！
Only 5 seconds left!
1個しか倒せてないよ！
I've only taken down one!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Good luck! Go for it!
Time's up!
ラプラスすごーい！1個！
Laplus, you're amazing! You got one!
後ろ向きでね
And while facing backwards, too.
絶対行きたい！
I definitely want to go!
絶対行きたい？
You definitely want to go?
あ、行きたい行きたい！
Ah, I want to go, I want to go!
メーター調整行きましょう！
Let's go with the meter adjustment!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
回ってるんだけど、私が
I'm the one who's spinning.
ゼータちゃんも回ってる
Zeta-chan is spinning too.
あと...あと12秒
12... 12 seconds left.
裏面だったなー今の
That was the back side just now.
これはもう後ろから！
This has to be from behind!
Time's up!
ゼータ、すごいヒーローです
Zeta, you're a great hero.
これむずいよ
This is so hard.
最後やからまつり行かせてください
Since it's the last one, let Matsuri go.
まつり先輩、行くぞー！
Matsuri-senpai, let's go!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
うま！うま！
Good! Good!
2個の時点で
At the point of two...
どんどん時間が過ぎてって...
Time is passing so quickly...
Time's up!
くそー、2個かー
Damn, only two?
一定集中で！
Focus on one spot!
アドバイスを活かしてやろうかね
Shall I put the advice to use?
トワ様の挑戦！3, 2, 1, Go!
Towa-sama's challenge! 3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
惜しい！惜しい！
Close! So close!
あと10秒！頑張れ！
10 seconds left! Good luck!
Time's up!
え、これくそむずじゃん
Eh, this is damn hard.
Level 3
なんとこちら、ボム！
And here we have... boom!
うわー！ゾンビだー！
Whoa! It's a zombie!
ゾンビの動く的になってます
It's a moving zombie target.
気持ち悪いポーズもしてます
It's also doing gross poses.
トワちんからじゃあ行きましょう
Then let's go with Toachin.
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
あと1枚！頭の！
One more! The one on the head!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
Clear
ギリギリセーフ！
Barely safe!
なんかゾンビがたまに自我を持ち始めて
The zombie sometimes starts to have a will...
不思議な動きをするので皆様注意を
and does strange moves, so be careful.
行きたい！行きたい！
I want to go! I want to go!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
はやっ！はやっ！
Fast! So fast!
Clear
3秒で終わりました
It finished in 3 seconds.
あー！
Aah!
危ない！
Look out!
危ない、危ない！
Watch out, watch out!
怒り込んでる！
He's getting angry!
これまずいよ、これ！
This is bad, this is!
やっちゃった、やっちゃった...
I did it, I did it...
まずいよこれ！
This is bad!
今まつりちゃんが3秒で撃ち抜いちゃったということは...
Since Matsuri-chan shot it down in 3 seconds...
あの多分もう次ゾンビはこの動きしちゃいけないなーっていう風になって...
The zombie probably realized it shouldn't move like that next time...
えー！やばい学習するタイプだ！
Eh! Oh no, it's the type that learns!
学習しちゃいます。
It learns.
学習ゾンビなんだ。
So it's a learning zombie.
ちょっと待って、じゃあ次ラプ様先やる？
Wait, then should La+ go next?
先やる、先やる！
I'll go next, I'll go next!
主役が最後でしょー。
The star comes last, right?
3、2、1、ドドーン！
3, 2, 1, kaboom!
スタート！
Start!
当たるんかい！
It hits?!
なんで当たんだよ！
Why did it hit?!
あたまだけでいいよ！
Just the head is fine!
撃て撃て撃て撃て！いいよいいよ、補給する！
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot! Good, good, I'll resupply!
待ちなさい！
Wait!
当たりそう、当たりそう！
It's about to hit, it's about to hit!
頑張れ頑張れ！
Hang in there, hang in there!
当たりそうだよ！あと5秒だよ！
It's about to hit! 5 seconds left!
あー！痛い痛い！
Aah! It hurts, it hurts!
そういうゲームになっちゃったじゃん！
It turned into that kind of game!
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
やばい、ちょっと途中我慢できなかった。ムカつきすぎて。
Man, I couldn't hold back halfway. I got too annoyed.
最後の挑戦はゼータ！3、2、1、ゴー！
The final challenge is Zeta! 3, 2, 1, go!
スタート！
Start!
めっちゃ動く、めっちゃ動いてる！
It's moving so much, it's moving a lot!
めっちゃ動いてるよ！
It's moving a lot!
おー、すっげー！私も動くからな！
Oh, awesome! I'm gonna move too!
オッケーだ！いやいやこれ、本物サイズ？
Okay! No way, is this life-sized?
頑張れ、頑張れ！あと1枚だよ！
Go for it, go for it! Just one more!
当たらない！
It won't hit!
顔いっちゃえ！あー危ない！
Go for the face! Ah, watch out!
すごかった、本当に。
That was amazing, really.
ポイントは... 2ポイントでしたー！
The score... was 2 points!
わー！すごーい！
Whoa! Awesome!
Guys! みんなー！
Guys! Everyone!
Should we see who got the most points in this fest?
Should we see who got the most points in this test?
おおー！で、めっちゃいい勝負。
Ooh! And it's a very close match.
まつりが12点。はい。で、トワちんが11点。
Matsuri has 12 points. Yes. And Towa-chin has 11 points.
はい。で、ゼータが10点。そしてラプラスが...
Yes. And Zeta has 10 points. And La+ has...
14点！
14 points!
4点！4点！
4 points! 4 points!
ラプラスが最下位！
La+ is in last place!
ちょっと待って、1位のほう選んでよ。
Wait, pick the one for 1st place.
Wooow! Congrats! すごーい！おめでとー！
Wooow! Congrats! Awesome! Congratulations!
You guys did very well! みんな本当にとにかく頑張ったね！
You guys did very well! Everyone really worked hard!
And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun.
I can't wait to see how much more you can improve
your aiming skills in the future, like me.
おい。何何何？ちょっと...
Hey. What, what, what? Hey...
Um, I'm... I'm talking here.
おい！こぼの話を聞いてよ！
Hey! Listen to Kobo!
Anyway, Zeta...
You still have a long, long way to go to become a full-fledged secret agent, okay?
Yeah, let's have a match one day!
Bye! See ya-!
あ、まだあった、こっちだね。やばいやばい、まつりちゃんもよ。
Ah, there was more, this way. Oh no, Matsuri-chan too.
あー行くからね！
Ah, here I go!
ふぅ、あー。すごいゲームだった。びしょ濡れだよ。
Phew, ah. That was a crazy game. I'm soaking wet.
濡れちゃったよ、水鉄砲で。すごかったね。
I got wet from the water gun. It was crazy.
びしょ濡れになっちゃった。
I ended up soaking wet.
服も着替えなきゃ。
I have to change my clothes too.
でも今日は告知があるって聞いたんだけど...
But I heard there's an announcement today...
みんな準備できてる？
Is everyone ready?
ちょっとアドブレイクかな。
Maybe a little ad break.
では、告知です！お願いします！
Now, here's the announcement! Please!
じゃじゃーん！うわー、まぶしい！
Ta-da! Wow, so bright!
すごく輝いてる。エンジェルみたいな衣装。
It's shining so much. An angel-like outfit.
可愛くない？天使のコスチューム。
Isn't it cute? An angel costume.
みんな私のこと怖いって言ってたけど...
Everyone said they're scared of me, but...
今は怖くないでしょ？だって私...
You're not scared now, right? Because I'm...
一番清楚な人だから。清楚ゼータ。
The most "seiso" person. Seiso Zeta.
清楚ゼータ来た。
Seiso Zeta is here.
どう？可愛い？可愛いでしょ？
How is it? Cute? It's cute, right?
真っ白だし。衣装も可愛いよね。
It's pure white. The costume is cute too, right?
Gimana guys? Karena kapan lagi bisa lihat Seiso Zeta ya guys.
How about it guys? Because when else can you see Seiso Zeta, guys?
Berkostum, ber-cosplay sebagai angel-angel gitu. Lucu, iya iya Zeta lucu lucu.
Dressed up, cosplaying as an angel like that. Cute, yeah yeah, Zeta's cute cute.
Aku mau, siapa yang mau? Aku aku!
I want it, who wants it? Me, me!
But we don't stop here because obviously there's gonna be so many more items.
And we're gonna introduce them now.
じゃあ、こちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
Now, please take a look at this! Here you go!
じゃじゃーん！数えたら6個くらいかな？
Ta-da! If I count them, there are about 6?
すごくない？
Isn't it awesome?
That's so cool!
So we have an acrylic diorama,
which you can put on your table.
Later we will explain.
We'll explain more later.
And we have a cap. No cap, okay?
We have a plushie nuigurumi!
We have a plushie!
And not only that, there will of course be voice...
And not only that, there will of course be a voice...
Sorry, why did I say that? "Voise"?
Sorry, why did I say it like that? "Voise"?
There will be voice pack.
There will be a voice pack.
And also bonus card as well.
And also a bonus card as well.
Who wants bonus cards?
Me!
So I bet you guys are interested in this, yeah definitely.
So I bet you guys are interested in this, definitely.
Kalau kalian tertarik bakal ada enam item ya guys,
If you're interested, there will be six items, guys,
acrylic diorama, haori, kucing, eh kucing...
acrylic diorama, haori, cat, uh cat...
Ada topi, ada juga boneka.
There's a cap, also a plushie.
いっぱいありますよね。うんうん。
There are many, right? Hmm hmm.
Bonus card, this is also bonus card.
A bonus card, this is also a bonus card.
So yeah, definitely we're gonna get into it,
So yeah, we're definitely gonna get into it,
but stay, stay there.
but stay, stay right there.
We're not, we're not done yet.
We're not done yet.
はい、次どうぞ。
Okay, next please.
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
This is my acrylic diorama! So cute!
Alutera-mama sensei!
Thank you so much, sensei!
ママ、ありがとう！
Mama, thank you!
Mama's drawing is always so cute!
かわいいでしょうね？
It's cute, isn't it?
かわいい！
So cute!
ゼータ飛んでるよ。ほほ！
Zeta is flying. Hoho!
凄くない？
Isn't it amazing?
It's super duper cute!
I'm having an al— I was— I almost said allergic reaction.
I'm having an al— I almost said allergic reaction.
I am having a— do you know that cuteness aggression? Yeah.
I'm having a— you know that cuteness aggression? Yeah.
That's what I'm feeling. It's so cute!
Okay!
Of course we're gonna go to the next one,
with so much more. Hmm hmm hmm.
じゃあ、次どうぞ。
Well, next please.
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
何だと？羽織！
What was that? A haori!
This is Zeta— the Vesta Zeta haori!
I know that you guys would love to wear this at like events,
I know you guys would love to wear this at events,
or like concerts, or maybe you know,
or at concerts, or maybe...
for future fests, next fest.
for future fests, like the next fest.
I mean, you guys can wear it together.
You can like huddle up wearing the same haori,
You can huddle up wearing the same haori,
and it would be so cute, right?
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform,
so you guys can— this can be your uniform.
so this can be your uniform.
ライブの時とか、
Like during a live concert,
そう、かわいいでしょう？
yeah, it's cute, right?
Like if everyone like uses it together, it's gonna be so cute.
If everyone wears it together, it'll be so cute.
Lucu banget guys, haori.
It's so cute, guys, the haori.
Aku nggak tahu mau ngomong apa, pokoknya ini keren banget,
I don't know what to say, basically this is so cool,
karena desainnya tuh pertama simpel,
because first off, the design is simple,
terus belakangnya tuh kelihatan Zeta.
and then on the back, you can see Zeta.
Terus nggak norak gitu lho guys.
And it doesn't look tacky at all, guys.
Kayak keren aja, kayak simpel, keren, cool.
It just looks cool, like simple, stylish, cool.
Jadi kalian juga pakainya bisa ke mana aja,
So you can wear it anywhere,
nggak harus kayak konser-konser doang.
it doesn't have to be just for concerts.
You can like wear this like outside of concerts as well,
You can wear this outside of concerts too,
cause like it's like a sophisticated...
because it's like a sophisticated...
I wouldn't say elegant... It's like a cool-looking,
like toned down haori, you know?
like a toned-down haori, you know?
So, befitting for me,
the coolest secret agent.
Okay, anyways!
Anyway!
There's more!
次の...
The next...
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
ジャジャーン！ワォ！
Ta-da! Wow!
Uwe—
Uweee cap!
The "Uweee" cap!
I almost choked on myself!
It's so good! It's a baseball cap.
It's so cool! You can use this to shield yourself from the sun,
like I do, because I hate the sun.
There's like "uweee" written on top of the cap.
It says "uweee" on top of the cap.
かわいい、「うええ」書いてるよ。
It's cute, it says "uweee."
そう、そう、そう。ゼータのセリフ「うええ」って書いてる。
Yeah, it has Zeta's catchphrase "uweee" written on it.
かわいいでしょう？
Cute, right?
Of course there's like my neko— ah not neko...
Of course there's my cat— ah not cat...
my hair buns, kuping Zeta.
my hair buns, Zeta's ears.
There's my hair buns there and my...
There are my hair buns and my...
ribbon, I would call this ribbon.
ribbon, I'd call it a ribbon.
Ignore the whiskers, but...
if you can ignore the whiskers, those are not cat whiskers.
if you ignore the whiskers, they're not cat whiskers.
But it's cute! You can wear it, a cap!
But it's cute! You can wear it, it's a cap!
Buy this cap! It's a good cap, no cap!
ははは！かわいい！
Hahaha! So cute!
Topi ya guys, apalagi panas-panas,
It's a cap, guys, especially when it's hot,
harus pakai topi nggak sih guys, panas-panas?
you gotta wear a cap when it's hot, right guys?
Apalagi silau gitu, keren kalau pakai topi lho guys.
Especially when it's bright, it looks cool with a cap, guys.
うんうんうん。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Terus keren lagi, hitam gitu topinya.
And it's cool, the cap is black like that.
Keren, keren, keren.
Cool, cool, cool.
まだあるのかな？
Is there more?
うん、あると思う。
Yeah, I think so.
じゃあ、次どうぞ。
Well, next please.
うーー！
Ughhh!
I... うーー...
I... ughhh...
it's... it's so cute!
It's a— with the cat headband,
it's called the "Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie".
Arigato!
Thank you!
It looks like a cat, I know, but I swear it's not. Okay, it's not. It's...
um... if you notice, it's based on my Cat Day KV. So it's so cute, right?
みんな あの Cat Day の時覚えてる？
Everyone, do you remember that Cat Day?
これ、This is the good from last time. It's so cute, right?
This... This is the good from last time. It's so cute, right?
Look at those eyes! It's so cute! I want to squish it and...
just jumble it up! It's so cute!
And she's like sleeping because, um, I heard that cats nap for 16 hours,
although that has nothing to do with me, I'm just saying.
Um, it's very cute! It's like sleeping.
うーん、眠そう、眠そうゼータちゃん。
Mmm, looks sleepy, sleepy Zeta-chan.
眠いゼータちゃん。可愛い！
Sleepy Zeta-chan. So cute!
Buy it or else! Or else, you don't want to miss this
because everyone liked the Cat Day KV. You won't miss it. Okay.
Even more, let's see. Next please!
次、お願いします！
Next, please!
ボイス！ワー！ボイス！ボイス！
Voice! Wah! Voice! Voice!
And it's titled 'A Fateful Meeting'.
Last but not least, there's also a bonus for who purchases the full set.
Okay, フルセットを買ってる人がボーナスを貰えるぞ。
Okay, those who buy the full set will get a bonus.
Okay okay. Kalian dapat bonus kalau kalian beli full set, okay?
Okay okay. You get a bonus if you buy the full set, okay?
じゃ、Last one please. 最後、お願いします！
Then, last one please. Last one, please!
ジャジャーン！Here's the bonus! おー！
Ta-da! Here's the bonus! Oh!
It's the limited edition. You'll get my signature. Okay?
It's so good, it's like handwritten signature and all that. おー！
It's so good, it's like a handwritten signature and all that. Oh!
It's the best! It's limited, so get it now!
Limited, スペシャルだよね。一番、まあスペシャル。うーん...
Limited, it's special, isn't it? The most special one. Mmm...
Of course, um, it's a little ad break, but we're not going to stop there
because I, even though it's my birthday, I want to give to you wings instead. Yeah!
But it's not over yet. これで終わりじゃないよ。
But it's not over yet. This isn't the end.
It's my birthday, but I also want to give you a present as well.
So... aren't you excited? Okay, let's go get your present! Woo!
Are you guys ready!?
Goin', goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin', goin' my way, just leave me alone
止めらんない熱に任せて
Let myself go, caught up in the unstoppable heat
こりごりだ Rule は Break it down
I'm fed up, the rule is break it down
我慢できない Let me free
I can't stand it, let me free
目が眩んでしまいそうな
Blinded by the sight,
出立ちのマーメイド 憧れてたっけ
of that mermaid I used to aspire to be?
But then, 今は何も響かない
But then, now nothing resonates with me
I know who I am, I
Brand-new には赤目
Brand-new, red eyes...
今は完全無視よ
Now I'm completely ignoring it
なんでもありの Greedy style
Anything goes, greedy style
ダサい諦めも興味ないの
I have no interest in uncool resignation
ありのままでいたい
I want to be as I am
Goin', goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin', goin' my way, just leave me alone
止めらんない熱に任せて
Let myself go, caught up in the unstoppable heat
こりごりだ Rule は Break it down
I'm fed up, the rule is break it down
我慢できない Let me free
I can't stand it, let me free
We are special でしょう
We are special, aren't we?
揺るがない Pride
Unwavering pride
それだけでいいの
That's all I need
たらればだらけの
Full of 'what ifs'
No No Night
If you break it down, break it
We are special でしょう
We are special, aren't we?
誰に笑われても
Even if anyone laughs at me
私は歌うよ
I will sing
Unfair ばかりの
In this unfair...
世界など break it down, break it
...world and such, break it down, break it
進め
Move forward
I just don't care about you
ハイテクなメイクやファッション
High-tech makeup and fashion
自分には構わないよ
I don't care about it for myself
好みと心 誰の物でもないでしょ
Preferences and heart belong to no one else, right?
いい加減に大人だよね
I'm an adult now, after all
Ini Zeta abadi
This is eternal Zeta
Hanya tidak sempurna tapi sepenuhnya diriku
Not perfect, but fully myself
でも今は楽しいよ
But now it's fun
ありのままでいられるから
Because I can be as I am
Goin', goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin', goin' my way, just leave me alone
止めらんない熱に任せて
Let myself go, caught up in the unstoppable heat
こりごりだ Rule は Break it down
I'm fed up, the rule is break it down
我慢できない Let me free
I can't stand it, let me free
We are special でしょう
We are special, aren't we?
揺るがない Pride
Unwavering pride
それだけでいいの
That's all I need
たらればだらけの
Full of 'what ifs'
No No Night
If you break it down, break it
We are special でしょう
We are special, aren't we?
誰に笑われても
Even if anyone laughs at me
私は歌うよ
I will sing
はびこるアンバランスなこの世界
This world, overrun with imbalance,
Break it down
Break it to smash
Can't break me down, breaking me
Break it down, break it down
Let's go!
Break it down
Break it to smash
Break it down, break it down
Goin' goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止めらんない熱 身任せて
Let myself be consumed by the unstoppable heat
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of it, the rule is to break it down
我慢出来ない Let me free
Can't hold it back, let me free
Thank you everyone!
That was Break It Down!
Zecretary, if you like it,
make some noise!
Break it down
Break it to smash
Can't break me down, breaking me
Break it down, break it down
Break it down
MISSION COMPLETE!
MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, ZECRETARY!
YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! :D
LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER...!
KEEP BREAKIN' IT DOWN!